export const quizSubject = "PT2 - NUMB - Stat & ALGEBRA";

let questions = [
  {
    "numb": 1,
    "question": "Expand and simplify the expression (x + 4)(x - 2).",
    "answer": "x^2 + 2x - 8",
    "options": [
      "x^2 + 2x - 8",
      "x^2 - 2x - 8",
      "x^2 + 6x - 8",
      "x^2 - 6x - 8"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 2,
    "question": "Factorise the quadratic expression x^2 + 8x + 15.",
    "answer": "(x + 3)(x + 5)",
    "options": [
      "(x + 3)(x + 5)",
      "(x + 1)(x + 15)",
      "(x - 3)(x - 5)",
      "(x + 2)(x + 6)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 3,
    "question": "Solve the quadratic equation x^2 - 5x - 14 = 0 by factorising.",
    "answer": "x = 7 or x = -2",
    "options": [
      "x = 7 or x = -2",
      "x = -7 or x = 2",
      "x = 14 or x = -1",
      "x = 5 or x = -14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 4,
    "question": "A fair six-sided die is rolled and a coin is flipped. What is the probability of rolling an even number and flipping a head?",
    "answer": "1/4",
    "options": [
      "1/4",
      "1/2",
      "1/3",
      "2/3"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 5,
    "question": "Find the Highest Common Factor (HCF) of 10a^3b^2 and 15a^2b^4.",
    "answer": "5a^2b^2",
    "options": [
      "5a^2b^2",
      "30a^3b^4",
      "5ab",
      "15a^3b^4"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 6,
    "question": "Expand and simplify the expression (x + 3)(x - 5).",
    "answer": "x^2 - 2x - 15",
    "options": [
      "x^2 - 15",
      "x^2 + 2x - 15",
      "x^2 - 2x - 15",
      "x^2 - 8x - 15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 7,
    "question": "Factorise the quadratic expression x^2 + 7x + 10.",
    "answer": "(x + 2)(x + 5)",
    "options": [
      "(x + 1)(x + 10)",
      "(x + 2)(x + 5)",
      "(x - 2)(x - 5)",
      "(x + 7)(x + 3)"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 8,
    "question": "Two fair dice are rolled. What is the probability that the sum of the scores is 7?",
    "answer": "1/6",
    "options": [
      "1/12",
      "1/9",
      "1/6",
      "7/36"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 9,
    "question": "Find the Highest Common Factor (HCF) of 12xy^2 and 18x^2y.",
    "answer": "6xy",
    "options": [
      "3xy",
      "6x^2y^2",
      "6xy",
      "18x^2y^2"
    ]
  },
  {
    "numb": 10,
    "question": "Solve the quadratic equation x^2 + 5x - 6 = 0 by factorising.",
    "answer": "x = 1 or x = -6",
    "options": [
      "x = -1 or x = 6",
      "x = 2 or x = -3",
      "x = 1 or x = -6",
      "x = -2 or x = 3"
    ]
  }
];

export { questions };
